One touch!
Well, well, man.
That jump in the glass this year has a punchable face.
About the three-man block for you,
could you please leave the timing up to me?
I knew that we'd be able to pull it off!
Total defense begins!
For When the three-man block changes,
it сам明日 gives you their lore!
Which has strong interest and fears 12.
Why you sayin tes a way to hang on with you?
No one's hidden in total unless everyone in any place isn't Nerede on earth!
Now at this stage,
when it passes away,
just a little time to through the rain.
So it seems like we need to draw down
The air is getting każdy on Earth
What you want to have to do with your head
I don't give us an idea of AdWords
Oh
Damn nice received Isinoya all thanks to you because you had it on since a tight course
You know the timing on that block. Oh, thanks
Now I get it
That block wasn't meant to stop was you waka it was meant to guide the ball exactly where they wanted
Nice teamwork boys. Oh, it's kind of like mobbing isn't it, huh? What's mobbing?
It's a type of behavior that smaller prey birds used to protect themselves
They will work together to gang up and harass a larger predatory bird to drive it off
That's a pretty badass metaphor. Did you come up with that yourself?
They were able to take control of the flow by using that connecting block to their advantage
It's exactly what we've been pushing for yeah
This total defense is cool, huh?
Even if we can't stop and we're blocking we have a fighting chance against who she walker with this technique. I
Didn't think it was possible, but they got to one of his spikes this game is turning out to be a good one
Damn it. Those bozos are squandering away the second set too
What the heck's wrong with this guy? Maybe grandpa needs a nap
Give us a good one
Huh?
Seriously?
That's how you do it!
Alright! Now's our chance! Let's take the set!
They might have gotten an easy point with that last serve, but let's pick up the pace guys.
Right!
Asahi! You got this!
Ghost game!
Yeah! Good job!
Here it goes!
Okay!
Not to big scary guy?
Makes sense since they're likely helping him conserve his stamina for the long game.
And...
It's a feint!
Sorry! It's headed on the...
Ishiya!
It's a feint!
Sorry! It's headed on the...
RACE!
Not just yet! We're two points shy!
Don't be such a downer dude!
Looks like the rotating Ushiwaka to the back!
Not good! Now we have to survive his serve!
Not good. Now we have to survive his serve.
Got it!
Get that over the neck!
Tanaka!
On it!
Chance ball!
Jimmy!
Where is he going?
A dump?
NOOOOO!
It's time to show them...
...that I do more than just support Ushiwaka.
Burners!
Not too shallow.
Nice! Shirobu!
I shouldn't have touched that.
I'm sorry, Nishinoya.
No!
I wouldn't have been able to get that either way!
No time to relax, guys!
Right!
Ah! They beat us the set point first!
Is something the matter?
Maybe I'm just imagining it, but I think there's something weird about my brother today.
Something seems off.
Well, I noticed the fire in his eyes burning brighter than normal!
If she noticed that...
I guess that means he might actually have more friends than just Tadashi.
Is this going out?
Nope.
Kaba!
Left side!
It's a three-man block!
Yeah!
The block out!
Woohoo!
Nice one, bro!
That makes this a deuce now.
Alright!
We're counting on you, Hinata!
Get them back for the beating they gave us in the first set!
Hm!
Huh?
Listen up.
So I guess they can't put Sugawara back in again, can they?
Right.
There's a rule that you can't switch in the same player twice during the same set.
We can breathe now that we survived Ushiwaka's serve.
But it's critical we stay sharp here, at least with Hinata at the front.
We should have an advantage here, guys!
Give us a nice serve, Suki!
Uh!
It's a one touch!
Listen up.
In the event that they're able to receive one of my serves, the odds are that they'll try
to follow it up with a quick attack.
So I jump at number five.
Chance ball!
Bring it!
Rubble bat!
Uh!
Competitive people are insane!
My heart can't take this!
Nice, Kageyama!
That was good, Mr. King of the Court.
Tsukishima!
Hell yeah!
That puts us back on top!
Now we have some breathing room with that set point.
Come on, Karasuno!
This might be pretty obvious, but I'm assuming it's difficult to score multiple points in succession.
Volleyball is designed to give both sides a chance to attack, so you're correct.
And not to mention, as we approach the end, both sides get more keen on putting it away.
But still, each side must continue to whittle down their opponent's defenses.
The most important factor isn't pure height and power, or the ability to consistently follow-up plays, or even maintaining your stamina and composure.
The main component to winning comes down to having the amount of energy it takes to earn one point after another.
I'm impressed that they're able to make such strong serves this late in the set.
Sorry, that's long!
Kageyama, push it over!
I got it!
Good job!
That's a chance ball!
That little piece!
Is he going for a feint?
He's going that way?
Good!
That'll put him at one and a half blockers!
Damn, that little decoy ace of theirs!
Did he intentionally set to the number five because he knew you were watching number ten?
Great set, buddy boy!
No, I was a little too early!
It's my fault!
You don't have to be so hard on yourself!
I know it would really piss me off to have someone like Hina to dart around in front of me, huh?
So please keep tearing up the court, you weirdos!
You good for nothing morons!
Shira Torizawa just called their first time out!
First time out!
We started playing
Good speed train!
We're not done!
SHIRA TORIZAWA
Surprisingly, Karasuna's giving us a run
for our money. But still, there's no
reason to panic at their little gimmicks.
Come on, guys. All we need to do is score points
the exact same way we always do.
Let's break their streak!
Right!
SHIRA TORIZAWA
When the game started, I was expecting a slaughterfest
by Shiratorizawa, but this is way
more fun. How's Karasuna a dark horse?
No kidding. Weren't they at championship
school a while back?
Oh, right. They might pull it off again, too,
since they have a strong lineup with Nishinoya
from Chidi Yoriyama, Kakeyama from
Kida first, and Asahi from Sekadai.
No matter how impatient
or tired you get, you can't
start slacking.
You can't let them get those last two points!
I think both sides are thinking exactly
that right now.
Come on, Karasuna.
If you lose this one, it'll really hamper morale
going into the next set.
Counting on you to give them
hell, Eta.
Alright.
ETA!
Give them a nice serve!
So Shiratorizawa's using their pinched server.
ETA! Go for it!
Alright.
Okay.
My bad!
Taichi!
Shirabu, above you!
Right!
ETA!
I got it, I got it!
Ghost key, for you!
Right!
Come to think of it, I guess he was the setter.
Focus on the next one, guys!
Right!
Give us a good serve!
Good serve!
Ah!
Daiji!
Crap!
Too short!
Good, it's off course.
What?!
A fast attack right there!
How'd they pull that out of their ass?!
That was incredible, Hinata!
I'm kinda having a hard time believing that!
That was amazing!
I know I sound salty, but their setter is ticking me off.
Show them what you got, Tanaka!
Got it!
Let us break.
Left side!
Yeah!
Vushuaka!
Three man block!
Wow!
Karasuno's Libero is nailing those receives every time now!
I'll be impressed once Vushuaka's playing up to his full potential.
You think you could take him on?
Yeah, but I don't feel like it.
Damn!
Sorry!
It was too close for the net!
Yeah!
Good job!
Don't give up!
We're so close!
Send it, Shirabu!
I got it!
Nice receipt!
Right side!
Yeah!
Nice guy, Jin!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
You know there's no way I'll be able to beat Vushuwaka.
It's just that our bodies, experience levels, and time we've devoted to the sport are very different.
There's just no way I can beat him.
I was hoping we'd be able to break through while we still had Hinata as a decoy.
Take a look at how anxious Hinata is in the back row.
I don't blame him, though. Both his serves and digs kind of suck.
If their number 5's guest blocks could score either 120 points or 0 points,
then my read blocks ought to safely net me around 75.
Although, I admit our blocking technique is a bit amateur compared to the guest blocks.
But I still like our odds, even if the audience prefers the more showy ones.
I absolutely won't let their setter get any sense of satisfaction or accomplishment from overcoming our blocks.
Persistently, tenaciously, nimbly, and absolutely...
I will not let them through.
Damn.
I'm going to continue layering the stress and pressure on them.
One touch!
Get it!
Cut that!
Good serve! I got it!
Your serves suck.
Your receives suck.
Even your setups and blocks are below average.
So why are you on the court?
To score points!
It's a break!
Amazing.
Awesome, Hinata!
The back attack at minus tempo has gotten even faster since Oikawa stopped it.
Taiji!
You gotta go for the ball!
Oh, whatever.
That was totally unblockable.
Nice one touch.
One more!
Yeah, but if Hinata hadn't come in and covered me, it would have just gotten blown away.
Nah, give yourself some credit.
It took that one touch to get it rolling in the first place.
Ishiro-bu.
Direct them to me.
Oh, crap!
It's going out.
I think.
If I guess wrong, I'll be the reason we lose.
It went off course.
It was going in?
I'm sorry!
Ushiwaka!
Alright, we've got three blockers.
And...
Jump!
That was really intense.
It was like the game's momentum changed in a single hit.
Don't let them pull ahead.
Let's try again.
Yeah!
Oh, damn, he's good.
Synchronized attack!
If we could just keep scoring points, there's no way we could lose.
Yeah!
Taichi, you got this!
Ushiwaka!
And...
Jump!
Miss it!
Return it!
We just have to open a path for our spiker.
This is exactly what I was waiting for.
A slight mistake created by...
Annoyance and panic.
...
There's just no way I could beat him.
I'm just...
I'm just hoping that I can stop a few of his spikes.
Who is he? Who knows?
It's amazing!
Karasuno took the second setback!
This was just one block.
Just one point out of 25.
And this is just a high school team.
If that moment ever does come to you,
that's the moment you'll fall in love with volleyball.
There wasn't any weakness in Ushiwaka's spike just now.
His run and jump were also in perfect form here.
If anything, that set was a little low, and maybe a little too close to the net.
I can't tell if Tsukishima honed in on that also, or if he's been patiently waiting for that exact chance.
At this time, I'd like to apologize for saying we couldn't stop it with blocks.
Clearly, I was wrong.
Huh?
And I do feel kind of bad because you look so concerned after I said it.
Uh, well, I just honestly believed we were in good hands because of Tsuki's hard work.
I know it seems kind of out of character for him, but he hates losing.
So I knew he would pull something together in the end.
Tsukishima!
Nice block, champ!
That block was awesome!
I'm sure they faced blockers of my level, but they didn't account for factors like Nishinoya's receives and the weirdo duo's quick attacks.
I knew those elements would put a lot of pressure on their setter.
You were really taking all those things into consideration?
Whoa, you got real issues, man.
If I know my brother, he was patiently waiting for that exact moment when Shira Torizawa would choke under pressure.
Wow, he waited a long time, but the payoff was sure worth it.
Tsukishima is really smart.
He has always struck me as the type of person who is always thinking and problem solving, whether it's in volleyball or in real life.
Sorry, I know he can spend a lot of time in his head.
No, not at all!
As I watched the game from above, I got the overwhelming feeling that the only thing on Tsukishima's mind was stopping that spike!
It makes me think that this is what it must be like for him when he solves a difficult problem on a test!
Tsukishima!
At one point was worth a hundred!
Good job!
Thank you!
Hey!
What's the-
Simmer down now, Hinata!
I know he's incapable of displaying any form of emotion, but he's now our beloved MVP!
Please, stop making a fuss.
Huh?
It was just one point.
The real battle begins now.
Yeah!
力すくじゃまだ届かずしまい
ギリギリで繋いで放つ願い
ただ、人やタイミングには恵まれて
へこたれずにいられてる
真っ向から勝負したい
迷ってもじっとこらえとこう
チャンスはそこにある
Oh、後は君次第です
うん、後は君次第
ひとりそう願いを叶えるもん
黙って明日を迎えるもん
後は君次第
今はゆとりもないし
悟るには早い
風の色目に染みる
ゆとり思って
サトリ脂め込んで
ココリ高く生きたい
No doubt
RIVER 後は君次第
です
うん、全部君次第
All right, Suki finally stopped Ushiwaka.
That's my bro. He makes me so proud. He might be blunt at times to keep to himself, but he's such a good egg, he's just trying to live his best life.
What, are you his mom or something?
Next, Haikyuu, one versus many.